POCO, WHERE YOU 'VE BEEN?!
HOW DARE YOU LEAVE THE HOUSE LIKE THIS?!
Please, Papa!
Papa, I'm sorry I left the
house, but where's my sister?
Well, where do you think?
She's out looking for you.
What?! No, Papa! Don't see that!
Tell me she didn't go out!
POCO, what's ailing you?
You're not behaving right.
My sister!
My sister! I don't know.
I'll see you
next time.
Consider this, dear.
Examine this rose in
bloom for but a moment.
Vibrant, fresh, and young, what
you see is a mirror of your youth.
Consider this fact
carefully, Mademoiselle.
From the first moment this flower
fully blooms, it begins to wither.
A shame, don't you think?
Only sixteen!
So sweet, so innocent and pure now!
So full of delicious life
energy, wonderful Lord Dio!
Those lacking in manners
are not fit to exist.
Now, Mademoiselle, I
offer unto you a choice.
Would you not care to enjoy your
youth and beauty for all eternity?
Fret not, my dear.
I shall not force my friendship
upon you like others might do.
You control your life.
You hold your destiny in your own hands.
You fiend. Eh?
How's that again?
You wear the flesh, but you're not a man.
Devil, go away!
Alas, although your acquaintance will
be brief, let me introduce my companion.
I present unto you, Doobie, as
regrettably I am not to your taste,
enjoy your time with him.
Au River, mademoiselle.
I knew it, me!
Doesn't matter, does it?
You're a zombie.
Your kind don't deserve any introductions.
Sister! Pukul!
Bitchy!
Bitch on your bright little face!
What did that?
What's he got under there?
His mask! Look at it!
Look down!
Run, run, run!
That zombie!
He's chock-a-block with
serpents! All sorts!
Venomous cobras,
flesh-eating asps and vipers!
Bit surprised, are ya?
They sank their fangs in his face!
And more than just once!
How wearisome!
I haven't the time to deal with
any more of Dio's foolish games!
Damn.
Very well done.
He squeezed out the poison. Good control.
He's learnt a great deal about blood
flow in a very short amount of time.
Baron Zeppeli!
He's helping our boy after giving
Jonathan his life energy when he died!
I'll use a bit of the
great hormone I possess
to turn these serpents
back on their master!
No!
Sister!
Hooker! Sister!
Guess who survived his time in hell, Dio?
You are alive, Jojo!
Curious?
I suppose.
Logically, that would then indicate!
You have killed my two knights.
Lord Dio!
We await your order to reduce him.
into a pile of bloody flesh.
Lord, let my fangs make
an impression on him.
Deal?
No, this one is for me.
He falls by my hand alone.
Don't misunderstand me, Jojo.
Honestly, this is something in
which I will take no pleasure.
We were raised in the same house.
And the prospect of turning
you into an United thing?
is not a happy one for me.
That's why I wanted you to be
quickly dispatched by my knights.
But it would seem, in the
end, I underestimated you.
Seeing you here, alive, brings me to
the realization that as an emperor,
I was being far too soft.
But now, now I'll put you to death
without a moment's thought or compunction!
I could say the same!
I will feel no hint of
guilt for your death!
But first I have a question, Jojo.
Whatever happened to that
mustachioed charlatan of yours?
You seem to have lost him.
Hear me, Dio.
It shames me as a gentleman to say this,
but I can no longer hold back the truth.
I, Jonathan Joestar,
have such hatred for you.
Vengeance consumes me!
I swear I will kill you!
Come, Jojo!
What are you doing?
Jojo, please step aside.
I have a prior claim.
It is my right to avenge
my friend's killing.
Zeppeli was a brave man and boon companion
through two decades of harsh training.
Dia, for his life, I shall now send
you to the bowels of hell itself!
No, wait, Dia.
Listen to me, D .O.
has hidden abilities for
which you are not prepared!
There's an interesting walk.
Apparently, with decades
of the proper training,
mere humans can enable themselves
to float through the air.
But in only a single night, I attained
power far surpassing that of any human guru!
You truly think you can
defeat me in this manner?
Like you were sleepwalking?
Fell for it, didn't you fool?
Thundercross split attack!
Uncanny!
In crossing his arms,
he can mount an attack while still
keeping his guard up for protection!
An incredible strategy!
No fighter has ever been
able to escape this move.
Oh no!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
I can't! I can't move!
He froze Dio!
Dio must have somehow chilled all
the moisture in his body at once,
turning him to ice in an instant!
Dio can't control his hormone!
He can't send it into Dio
unless his blood is flowing!
Struth!
That Dio's a fearsome
creature right enough.
He froze Dio's whole body at once!
How did you do this?
Oh, we are feeble, aren't we?
You imbecile, you dare think
you could lay a finger on me!
You're the one who's going to give
up your life like some mongrel!
Let's endeavor to give them
a good show, shall we? No!
Dio, stop it now!
It's time, Jojo!
You're the next I shall
dispatch to oblivion!
Dire!
Those hormone-filled roses
thorns do sting a bit.
Liar!
Insect, how dare?
How dare you wound me?
Wound my face?
Dyer, no.
Speed wagon! My sword! Catch!
Kyo!
I know exactly how to deal with you.
Dyer gave up his life, which showed
me just how vulnerable you are.
It will be very easy for me now.
You won't be able to stop it.
All I need to do is fill Bluford's
Sword of Luck and Pluck with Hamon,
and slice you with it!
You dare to touch me, filthy human.
You dare to touch me with your Hamon!
More disgusting than frog urine!
Your string of luck's run out!
Now you shall be father for my zombies!
They will gnaw the faces
right off your skulls!
Now we see!
He shows his true colors as someone
fit only to rule over a dung heap!
His cool, taut sophistication,
nothing but a cheap mask!
Now that he's had himself a nice,
humiliating taste of harmone, he
reveals his true, filthy self!
Straitzoe's my name.
No mercy.
Page would be my name. Jones!
Plant!
Born on!
Needle vein strike!
Roses are alive and vital!
So harmon will remain inside them?
flowing along with their life force.
But the same thing
cannot be said for steel.
It's necessary to make contact.
A great many of them are coming.
If you wish, I shall handle them for you.
From all the indications I've seen, that
bloke deals more swift than any leopard.
But with Zeppeli's Harmon,
Jonathan just might keep up.
Though, Dio is strong enough to pulverize
flesh and bone with a flick of his wrist.
For the both of them, it could be up to
what happens in the very first moment.
I will squeeze the life out
of you with my own hands!
I will cleanse the world
of your evil influence!
What?
He snatched up some roses
when I wasn't looking!
Come now!
Wait, that's good!
He circled around to the right!
Dio is blind on that side.
Take this, Dio!
No, damn it all!
He knows exactly what he's doing!
Yes, kill him!
He finally defeated Dio!
Defeated you fools?
Oh no, I can't move!
I'm frozen!
You're so feeble, Jojo!
Now weakling, you shall join
my other children of the night!
I've got your rubbery little
karate between my fingers!
So warm and springy!
A strangely pleasant? feeling.
A kick!
Enjoying this anguished Jojo?
One tiny little move and
this delicate blood vessel?
snaps in two like a wet ribbon.
With your carotid open, all
your blood will be mine.
Then I shall fill the vacancy
with my own Vampiric Essence,
and you will be my thrall!
We have to help him!
Zombies, to me!
Keep those peasants back.
I'm rather busy.
Nothing seems to stem
this tide of zombies.
We cannot provide any help.
Now, Shuichi, in your last moment of free
will, realize that the victory was mine!
No, Dio.
You've not won yet.
You've made a fatal mistake? How?
So you see Dio?
If you freeze me completely,
you'll not be able to continue
feeding on my life energy.
This means however that
my hormone is unaffected.
You can't block it as long as
I remain partially unfrozen.
Your tactics to say the
least are somewhat blah.
How long has the sword
been in those flames?
The metal blade is conducting
heat from the fire faster.
so that I can freeze it.
Hamon is blowing up the blade.
Sunlight yellow, overdrive!
He's done it.
Not exactly correct.
It's quite evident the Hamon
did not make it through.
My arm, my arm is frozen solid again.
I only briefly touched his face.
This isn't over, Jojo.
I have to admit, I must
admire your tenaciousness.
Really, I do.
And your ingenious use of the flame.
Truly marvelous example of quick thinking.
But really, Jojo, an emperor's
reach should exceed his grasp.
Just a touch on the arm is all it takes.
I can turn your whole body
to ice in two seconds!
The vampire essence!
He squeezed it out!
He's not done!
Jonathan won't give up!
Really?
The let's do battle stance?
You're not serious.
No matter how you prepare, Human
ability is extremely limited and finite.
Your Harmon training avails you nothing.
A mere monkey can never defeat a lion!
In comparison to my power, you
are but a mere monkey, Jojo!
You're wrong!
With true conviction, the human
race can overcome anything!
Let me demonstrate to just what
heights a human being can rise!
Don't waste your time, a
zombie is all you'll ever be!
Struth, his hand is burning!
Flames coming from his glove!
That might just have the power
to get through Dio's ice!
When this business is done,
which one of us will have fallen?
We'll find out, Dio!
Dio's blocking Jojo!
But no!
It's breaking through!
I'm disintegrating!
It can't be!
The pain, the burning, I can't!
My reign was to have lasted forever,
for centuries uncounted by man!
You had to be destroyed, Dio.
I will not die!
How did he shot energy from out of his
eye he came to within only mere inches of
incinerating my brain
far too close the last
act the demon refuses to
acknowledge his death?
Dio has fallen from the parapet!
Dio...
Look, he fainted!
He's worn out. Too right.
He's been in more fatal fights tonight
than a man should have in a lifetime.
But why would he shed tears
for an evil creature like that?
He weeps because they
spent their youth together.
Dio was like a brother to him.
But as for me, I could sing a song of joy.
Baron Zeppeli, were you watching?
He did it.
Jonathan Joestar did it.
Dio is dead.
It may sound an exaggeration,
but JoJo saved the world tonight.
The words will make you out and out.
You spent the day in your way.
Calling morning, running through the sun.
And in another valley.
We're on the lake.
My heart's coming out of the sky.
We stand there.
We'll be
right back.
da, da, da, da, da,
da,
da It appears that I'm
crying out from joy.
You must leave, Iran.
I want to stay like this.
Where is my body?